edin.com 2019-03-05

# Privacy and Security - Educational Insights®

Educational Insights, and its affiliated companies,  respects the privacy of its customers and takes precaution to ensure any information submitted to it via its web site or via e-mail is handled appropriately.

## What information about customers does EducationalInsights.com gather?

### Information you give us

We receive and store any information you enter on EducationalInsights.com. You provide information to EducationalInsights.com when you log in, search, purchase products, or communicate with customer service.

### Information automatically collected

We automatically receive and store certain types of information whenever you visit EducationalInsights.com For example, like most web sites, we use "cookies" (see below for more information on cookies).

### Our use of your information.

We use information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities with Educational Insights. By visiting our site, you agree that we may use identifiable information about you to expedite order processing, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, and customize EducationalInsights.com's content, layout, and services. These uses improve EducationalInsights.com and better tailor it to meet your needs.

## Does EducationalInsights.com disclose the information it receives?

As a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any emails to third parties outside of our affiliated companies.

## Protecting Children's Privacy

Educational Insights' products, although intended for use by children, are available for adult purchase only. Persons under 18 are not permitted to purchase products from Educational Insights. Persons under 18 are required to use the site under the supervision of a legal guardian.

### A special note for parents and legal guardians:

Educational Insights adheres to the U.S. Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA") and the guidelines of the Children's Advertising Review Unit ("CARU") of the Council of Better Business Bureaus, Inc. in our web Sites, online services and Apps directed to children under 13. Wherever we refer to "children" or a "child" in this Privacy Statement, we mean children under 13. Please help us protect your children's privacy by instructing them never to provide personal information (like their full name, e-mail address, home address, telephone number, etc.) without your permission. Private information identified as being gathered from a person under the age of 13 is used solely for completion of the requested action and immediately destroyed. This includes, but is not limited to, submissions to the Wish Lists, sweepstakes, and e-mail.

### A special note to kids:

If you are under 13, you should get your parent's or legal guardian's permission before giving out your contact information, like e-mail address or phone number, or any other personal information, to Educational Insights or to anyone else.

### What Are Educational Insights' Children's Privacy Practices?

At our web Sites, we do not collect personal contact information from children under 13 (like full name, e-mail address, phone number or home address) without consent of a parent or legal guardian except in special, limited circumstances described below. We do not ask for more information than is necessary for a child to participate in the activity. We take steps to prevent children from posting or publicly disclosing personal contact information, like name, phone number or e-mail address, online, without parental consent. We do not share any information collected on children under the age of 13 with any third parties.

### What Information Does Educational Insights Collect from Children Under 13 and How Is It Used?

To participate in special activities, like sweepstakes, we might ask your child to "register" for the "Activity." We ask your child to give us his or her name and your e-mail address, so that we can tell you that they have registered in an Activity. If we need more than an e-mail address and first name (or screen name) to enter your child in the Activity, award a prize, or offer the service, we will notify you, explain what information we need and why, and generally ask that you (not your child) provide it. When we ask for your permission, we will tell you what we will do with the information you or your child provides us, and how you can review your child's information and ask us to delete the information. With your verifiable consent, we may collect other personal information from your child such as a last name or home address when the information is necessary for a particular Activity.

In addition, we might ask you for your mailing address so that we can send to you, for your child, any prizes your child wins, or for your phone number so that we can contact you if your child has won. Any information we receive from you or your child in the above special circumstances will be deleted from our database once the Activity is concluded, and after any legally required period for keeping such information is complete.

We may use technology, like cookies or Google Analytics, to recognize visitors by their user name when they revisit our Site and to screen for age in accordance with COPPA.

### Can I Access, Update and Review Information You Have About My Child?

If you no longer wish your child to participate in an Activity or wish to remove the child's information, simply click on the link that is provided for removal or contact us at Educational Insights, 152 W Walnut Street, #201, Gardena, CA 90248. Upon proper identification, a parent or legal guardian may review the personal information we have collected about their child, update their child's contact details, request deletion, or refuse to allow further collection or use of the information.

Please note, however, if you ask us to delete your child's information, your child may not be able to participate in any Activities.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small file that a web server automatically sends to your computer when you browse certain web sites. Cookies are stored as text files on your hard drive and contain information that identifies a user, for example: login or username, passwords, shopping cart information, preferences, and so on. When a user revisits a web site, his or her computer automatically "serves up" the cookie, which establishes the user's identity, thus eliminating the need for the customer to reenter the information. Cookie technology also makes shopping cart technology possible. For example, when you select items that you intend to purchase in an online catalog, cookies make it possible for you to continue shopping and to "check-out" later. For more details about cookies, visit: [http://www.netlingo.com/lookup.cfm?term=cookies.](http://www.netlingo.com/lookup.cfm?term=cookies)
